The first practice we'll talk about,
第一种实践
is writing code in a way that is clean and modular.
是以整洁和模块化的方式编写代码
Data scientists often struggle with this when they first start coding,
数据科学家在第一次开始编码时
or even if they've been coding for years in a more research or academic setting.
或者即使已经在更学术的研究环境中编码多年 都需要为此努力
When you're working in industry,
在行业中工作
your code could potentially be used in production.
你的代码可能被用于生产
Production code just means code that is run on production servers.
生产代码就是指在生产服务器上运行的代码
For example, when you're on your laptop using software products like Udacity,
例如 当你在电脑上使用优达学城、
Google, or Amazon, the code that's running the service you're using is production code.
谷歌或亚马逊等软件时 正在运行服务的代码就是生产代码
Ideally, code that's being used in production should meet a number of
理想情况下 在生产中使用的代码应该满足许多标准
criteria to ensure reliability and efficiency before it becomes public.
以确保在公开之前的可靠性和效率
For one, the code needs to be clean.
首先 代码需要整洁
Code is clean when it's readable, simple and concise.
整洁要求代码可读、简单、精炼
Here's an example in plain English of a sentence that is not clean.
来看一个不整洁的自然语言句子示例
"One could observe that your shirt has been sullied,
"会有人看到你的衬衫被弄脏了
due to the orange color of your shirt that appears
因为上面有橙色
to be similar to the color of a certain kind of juice."
看起来像果汁的颜色"
This sentence is terribly redundant and convoluted.
这句话非常冗余复杂
Just reading this makes me frustrated.
仅仅是读出这句话就已经让我感到沮丧
This can be rewritten as,
这句话修改为
"It looks like you spilled orange juice on your shirt," and accomplish the same thing.
"你好像撒了橙汁在衬衫上" 也可以表达相同的意思
But this sentence is much more concise and clear.
修改后的表达更加简洁明了
Writing clean code is very important in an industry
在行业工作中编写整洁的代码非常重要
setting where on a team that's constantly iterating over its work.
因为团队的工作是在不断迭代的
This makes it much easier for yourself and others to understand and reuse your code.
整洁代码使你和他人都可以更容易地理解和复用代码
In addition to being clean,
除了整洁
your code should be modular.
你的代码还应该是模块化的
Meaning, your program is logically broken up into functions and modules.
这意味着 你的程序在逻辑上分解为了函数和模块
In programming, a module is just a file.
在编程中 模块就是指一个文件
Similarly to how you can encapsulate code in
你可以将代码封装为函数
a function and reuse it by calling the function in different places,
并在不同的地方调用函数来复用 与之类似
you can encapsulate code within a module or
你也可以将代码封装在模块或文件中
file and reuse it by importing it in other files.
然后通过将其导入其他文件来重复使用
We will see examples of this later.
我们稍后会看到这种示例
To you get a better understanding of what modular code is,
为了更好地理解模块化代码
try to think of it as putting your clothes away.
试着将它想象成存放衣服
Sure, you could just put all of your clothes in a single jar,
当然 你可以把所有衣服堆在一个抽屉里
but it wouldn't be very easy to find anything.
但这样很不容易找到目标
Maybe because you can't ever find anything,
也许你会因为
you have multiple reversions of the same shirt or
在想要寻找某些衬衫或袜子的时候找不到
socks because you repurchased them when he couldn't find them.
而重复购买了很多一样的款式
It will be much better if instead,
用不同的抽屉区分存放会好很多
you had a drawer for tee-shirts,
一个专门存放 T 恤
another one for just shirts,
一个专门存放衬衫
another for socks, and so on.
一个专门存放袜子等
With this design, if you need a nice outfit for an interview,
这样设计后 如果你需要一套合适的服装来面试
you don't need to worry about buying one just because he couldn't find the right clothes.
你不需要担心因为找不到合适的衣服而重复购买
If you need to tell someone else how to find the right shirt,
如果你需要告诉别人如何找到合适的衬衫
pants, and pair of socks,
裤子和袜子
it will be much easier with this design.
这种设计也会让别人的寻找更简单
The same is true in writing modular code.
编写模块化代码也是如此
Splitting a code into logical functions and modules,
将代码拆分为逻辑性的函数和模块
allows you to quickly find a relevant pieces of code.
可以使你快速查找相关的代码段
You can often generalize these pieces of code to be reused in different places,
你通常可以将代码概括为不同的片段 方便在不同的地方复用
to prevent yourself from writing extra unnecessary lines of code,.
防止自己编写额外不必要的代码行
Abstracting out these details into these functions and
将细节抽象为函数和模块
modules can really help in improving the readability of your code.
对提高代码的可读性帮助很大
Again, programming in a way that makes it easier for a team
再次强调 使团队更容易理解和迭代的
to understand and iterate on is crucial for production.
编程方式对于生产至关重要
In this lesson, you will get
在本课中 你将练习
practice writing code that is clean and modular to help you accomplish this.
编写整洁且模块化的代码来帮助你实现这一目标